[Theme song]
[intense music]
Oh, shut up! seed…
shut up! seed…
Shut up!
Everyone, everyone, everyone, everyone, shut up!
Shut up, go, go, go…
- [Echoing] Shut up!
- Aren't you telling me to shut up?
-This is live...
- ['Shut up' echoes again and again]
Shut up!
[The sound gets louder and repeats over and over again]
- [Rose's Laughter]
- [Music fades]
- [Upbeat music plays]
- Oh, what should I do?
[Continued laughter]
[Cheerful music continues to play]
Uh, what should I do?
[Kanghyuk in the video] Oh, shut up
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
[Rose] Ah, I want to debut
He said
You succeeded
- Ah, but the photo is so bad.
- [Kang Hyuk in the video] Shut up!
- ah…
[Myunghee] Mr.
this…
- [Interesting Music]
- Wow, this.
This is a completely unexpected development.
[Joeun’s laughter]
[Jo Eun] I have that expression on Secretary Kang’s face.
I should have seen it in real time
Wow, the reporters are so excited, huh?
[Jaehoon’s laughter]
Oh my
The ambitious parachute
I saw the bottom
[Jaehoon’s applause]
- [Jaehoon continues to laugh]
- It's not just good.
[Sighing] Baek Kang-hyuk
The reason I fall asleep alone is because
It's okay, though.
No, just for this one, it's like that.
Our hospital is on par
Ah, the hospital face
Doing shit
In the meantime
Ask for an increase in the budget for trauma surgery
Directly to me
I sent an email
- Email?
- [Joeun] Yes!
Do you know what I said?
If it is difficult due to hospital circumstances,
To the Minister
I would like to ask you directly
Isn't this meme?
Ah, something like that happened…
Ana, you insolent man…
I'm depressed, I'm depressed
Huh? Minister Kang is always making excuses.
There is no reason to kick him out.
[Heavy breathing]
No, it's just that
Do you just want to look around?
Let's take a chance for now, okay?
Baek Kang-hyuk is like that.
If you try hard
The day will surely come when you will buy and hit
[Interesting music fades out]
- [Jaehoon] Hmm
- [Sound of automatic door opening]
Director
I'm in big trouble
[Jaewon muttering] Blackwings
‘Blackwings’
- [Dark Music]
- [Jaewon]
‘Those medics too’
‘Known as a human weapon’
[Loud gunshot]
[Dark music stops]
‘Personal firearms, close range attacks… '
and…
- [Sound of tapping on table]
- Wow, this is no joke.
- [Dark sound effect]
- Wow...
- [Thumping music]
- [Sound of surprise]
[The pounding music stops]
Hey, number 1
Yes, No. 1 Yang Jaewon!
What are you doing?
I was doing nothing!
Don't you?
Why don't you do it?
The vital signs of patients in the intensive care unit
I also need to check IO.
I also have to study the thesis I gave.
Why are you stuck here, huh?
[Tsk mouth sound] Useless
- Huh? uh? uh?
- I'm looking into something like this, Mr.
- [Laptop closing sound]
- I will correct it again, again, again.
[Kanghyuk] Hey, Mr. Lee
- [Jaewon] I’m sorry
- Let's do well.
So that neither one gets tired
Well, well, professor, but...
ah…
I have a question.
I really just have no other intentions.
Really and purely
I'm asking because I'm curious.
Why, what?
[Jaewon] That…
At the International Peace Conference
The gap that suddenly went to the Blackwings...
I don't quite understand this...
[sigh]
Ah!
You're going to a more dangerous place.
Because if we go, there will be more seriously ill patients.
- [Muttering] So that's it...
- [Kang Hyuk] To make money
Yes?
[Kanghyuk] Oh, just, whatever.
I heard they pay a lot of money
Ah!
[Guide voice] Code black, code black
Emergency medicine, major trauma center
All medical staff
- Please come to the emergency room…
- what? suddenly?
[dark music]
- Disaster Protocol
- [Kanghyuk] Run
[Guide voice] … Emergency Medicine
Severe trauma center
All medical staff went to the emergency room...
[Call connection tone]
- [Rose] Professor!
- [Kang Hyuk] Gangster, what's going on?
- [Siren sound]
- [Rose] At Sowol Bridge
It was a collision involving about 60 vehicles.
I think it's quite big because of the fog.
- [Car alarm sound]
- Including 2 tour buses
Most vehicles are on the bridge
Rescue operation is in progress.
4 vehicles including one bus
They say he fell off the bridge.
[People moaning and screaming]
Ambulances are arriving now.
Come quickly
[Jaewon] Seriously injured
I think it's worth it
- [Siren sound]
- [Kanghyuk] We have to hurry
If the situation is like this
They'll be flocking to tertiary hospitals like us.
Transferred to a small hospital
Because something could go wrong with the patient
Okay? hurry!
[Man 1] This way, quickly!
[Man 2] This way!
[Woman 1] I will quickly transfer you to the treatment room.
[Woman 2] I’ll hurry
[Woman 3] Passing by
[Woman 4] I’ll pass by first.
[People's urgent voices]
[Woman 1] Quickly this way!
[Man 1] I’ll pass by first!
[Woman 2] I’ll pass by!
[Woman 3] Wait here for a moment…
[Man 2] Don’t lose consciousness.
- [Kang Hyuk] Wait!
- [People’s repeated urgent sounds]
[click button sound]
- Intubate and get a C-line.
- [Jaewon] Yes, I understand.
[Kang Hyuk] Gangster!
Secure as many operating rooms as possible
[Rose] Yes!
[Kanghyuk] Close your eyes
Please close your eyes
[telephone ringing sound]
- Yes, hello.
- [Kang Hyuk] Gangster!
Arrange all the residents.
Emergency medicine now
Everyone is mobilized, including interns.
Each department
- Especially all surgical aspects
- [Rose] Yes, I understand.
[Woman 4] Teacher Kim, this way!
[Man 3] I’ll send you straight to the prosecutor’s office!
[Man 4] Don’t lose your mind!
[Woman 5] Please call the orthopedic clinic!
[Rose] Professor!
Team leader Ahn Joong-heon is now
Patients are transported by helicopter.
[Doctor] One, two, three
[Jaewon] Ah! quickly
Luckily it's not open
gangster
- Orthopedic Surgery Notihae
- Yes, I understand.
-Why, why are you like this?
- Can I contact Team Leader Ahn?
- [Radio radio operating sound]
- No, why are you doing that, professor?
You have to go, patient, patient.
Team leader Ahn, this is Baek Kang-hyuk.
- Can you hear me?
- [Crackling radio sound]
- [Loud siren sound]
- Team Leader Ahn, can’t you hear?
Team leader Ahn!
This is Baek Kang-hyuk!
[Jungheon] Are you Professor Baek?
This is no joke
[Car alarm sound]
[Kang Hyuk] Even the cars that fell under the bridge
I heard there is
Has the rescue started over there?
[Jungheon] No, under the bridge
I couldn't even start
It's difficult to access the entrance now.
I'm going to walk down the rope.
- Okay.
- [Crackling radio sound]
Hey, Professor, go…
[Jaewon sounds embarrassed]
- We go to the scene.
- Yes?
Seriously serious trauma patients
It's there
No, still…
professor! no…
no…
ah…
[Dark music fades]
[News Anchor] Around 7:40 am today
Sowol Bridge occurred…
[Man] Up to 40 people
Simultaneous treatment is possible in the emergency room
Currently 38 people are being treated.
Soon after the first examination
We plan to link with each department.
[Joeun’s deep breathing]
yes
Manager Lim, this time in the emergency medicine department.
I'll have to give it some trouble.
Treat patients as early as possible in the early stages of an accident.
You should get a lot
That way, you can quickly fix it.
It helps, um
[Jaehoon] Oh my, it’s been a while, huh?
If all those slanderers are brought in,
I wondered what would happen
Baby, money again
How much did you pour, Mr.
I won't even pay the electricity bill.
Manager
Those words...
No, if others hear it
[disapproving breath]
Because I have money
Because I don’t want to get seriously injured
disaster protocol
I think it's activated, huh?
Oh my, Director, can’t that be true?
No, such a major accident
Even in the media
Because it attracts a lot of attention
Let’s be careful, that’s it.
No, to save the lives of those seriously injured.
Baek Kang-hyuk, that bastard
How hard can you be, huh?
If done well, it will be Baek Kang-hyuk's personal achievement.
If something goes wrong, you'll die at Korea University Hospital!
Let's prevent such unfortunate events in advance, okay?
- Oh, isn't that right, Manager Lim?
- Yes, it's me, Chief of Staff.
Professor Baek is not here right now.
[Jaehoon] Yes, so…
what? No?
Mr. Ai, I have to see the patient.
Where are you going?
[Manager Lim] Yes, I definitely
That's what I said
No, but well, this much
Coverage is possible at the emergency medicine department.
Hey, so where did you go?
Yes, there
Hyun, I went to the scene, to the scene.
Are you going to personally take the seriously injured people?
[helicopter sound]
[dark music]
[Sirens sound in the distance]
[Captain] Professor, we have arrived.
Shall we go on the bridge?
Or should we go under the bridge?
Captain
- Let's go right under the bridge.
- [Captain] Yes, professor.
[Jaewon’s scared voice]
[Man] This way, this way!
This way!
- [Woman's scream]
- [Man] Oh, quickly, quickly.
[Noisy sound]
[People shouting urgently]
How is the situation?
Fortunately, the detour was open
Ambulances are arriving now.
When the casualties are rescued
I'm going to escort you right away.
No, we have to sort it first.
Those who were rescued
- Please gather them all in one place.
- Yes
[Jaewon] Starting with people who seem in a hurry
Should I treat it?
[Kang Hyuk] We are here
I'm not here for treatment.
I'm here to sort it out.
people here
I have no authority to pronounce death
we do our best
Patients who can be saved
We need to classify patients who don't
For now, you
Triage conscious patients first.
[Jaewon] What about the professor?
We need to start by classifying the dead.
Keep your mind strong
yes
[People shouting urgently]
[Beep loudspeaker howling]
[loudspeaker alarm sound]
- [Rescuer 1] Three, two…
- [Rescuer 2] Please help me
[Rescuer 1] One, two, three, four!
- [Beep loudspeaker howling]
- [click button sound]
[Kang Hyuk] Come on!
From now on, all rescuers
You have to go through us.
Never!
Do not transport by ambulance right away
based on me
Those who are conscious, on my right
If you are unconscious, go to my left!
Including deaths
- Let's move quickly!
- [Rescuers] Yes!
- [Rescuer 1] … Two, three, four!
- [Jaewon] Professor
- [Rescuer 2] Move here
- [Rescuer 3] Yes!
- [Rescue worker 4] Triage the patient!
- [Rescuer 5] Do you have a defibrillator?
[People shouting urgently]
You can stop.
He died
I don't have time to be like this
Let’s quickly go rescue another patient.
[Rescuer 6] Yes
[rustling sound]
[Rescuer 7] Please look here!
[Rescuer 8] Patients
I'll move this way
[Rescuer 9] One, two, three, four!
[Rescuer 10] This way
Quick, quick!
[Rescuer 11] This way
Go there!
[People continue to shout urgently]
- [Noisy sound]
- [Dark music fades]
[Man 1] Measures
Shouldn't it be set up, huh?
- [Continuously noisy]
- [News is playing]
[Man 2] Minister
Now Professor Baek Kang-hyuk
in the field
We are triaging patients.
- [Myunghee] Professor Baek?
- [Man 2] Yes
[News Anchor] Acceptable
The emergency room is expected to be severely inadequate...
- [Heavy music]
- [Girl crying] Oppa
[Kanghyuk] Oh, it’s okay, it’s okay
[Girl] Oppa
It hurts…
My brother hugged me tightly
when falling
[Kang Hyuk] Yes, you are
I will definitely save you too
Just wait a little while
yes
[Rescuer 1] Ah, quickly, quickly.
This way, this way!
[Rescuer 2] Everyone is out
Quick, quick!
[Jungheon] Professor!
please look here
[Rough breathing]
I have a pulse and breathing.
I'm unconscious
Pipe torn during fall
It looks like I got stabbed.
Because the bleeding was so heavy
I cut it like that
Well done
[Rescuer 3] Please look here!
[Kang Hyuk] Bring the thread and the suture tool.
- Bite thread number 2
- [Jaewon] Yes
[Rescuer 4] Please get out of the way.
It passes by
- [Jaewon] Here it is
- [Kanghyuk] Wait a minute
[Jaewon’s heavy breathing]
[Repeated urgent sounds around]
[Heavy music]
[Jaewon] Uh…
Professor, too deep
Aren’t you trying to shame me?
I have to stop the bleeding first.
Can’t you tell just by looking at it?
Do you know how to treat a patient with a penetrating injury?
Make a midline incision
- Stop the bleeding first.
- [Sound of repeated sewing]
Then pull this out
yes, i understand
Me?
Take this patient to the helicopter
Enter the operating room
As soon as I finish sorting
I'll follow you
That classification
Can I do it, Professor?
[Kanghyuk’s heavy breathing]
[Kanghyuk] Just look at you
Is it someone who will die or someone who will live?
Can you judge?
Oh, that's not it
I'm not confident, Professor.
I'm confident
Trust me, trust me, do you trust me?
- [Nervous music]
- [Woman’s sharp scream]
- [Rescuer 1] Are you okay?
- [Rescuer 2] Move here
[Kang Hyuk] This patient is the one who will live.
So
Go and make sure you survive
Okay?
yes
Yes!
[ECG meter beeping sound]
[Jaewon] Now, be careful, Teacher Jang Mi.
Teacher Rose!
The operating room opened, right?
I'm on standby. What about the professor?
I'm still on site.
Go in first with Teacher Jangmi.
Now, let's go
[Shoot water sound]
- [The sound of water stops]
- [Sound of brushing]
- [Dark Music]
- [Jaewon’s heavy breathing]
[Kanghyuk’s voice rings out]
I'm confident
Trust me, trust me, do you trust me?
[ECG meter beeping sound]
[Jaewon mutters]
First, make a midline incision.
Stop the bleeding first
Blood pressure…
I can do it [heavy breathing]
[Rose] Teacher
Come to your senses
This is Jaewon, the housekeeper.
If the surgeon shakes
everyone is shaken
[Jaewon's trembling breathing]
[Jaewon’s nervous breathing]
[Jaewon] Surgery
Let's get started
scalpel
[Inhaler operating sound]
[Continued inhaler operating sound]
[Woman's moaning and crying]
[Woman's sharp scream]
Because it’s an open fracture
Please wipe carefully.
[Rescuer] Yes, I understand.
[Woman's repeated cries mixed with screams]
Because it takes painkillers
It'll be okay in a little while
[Rescue worker] Professor, this…
Found in patient's belongings
I think you have diabetes.
I see you carry insulin with you.
[Rescuer's heavy breathing] What should we do?
This patient needs to be transferred immediately.
[Rescue worker] To which hospital?
Shall we transport it?
Transferred to Korea University Hospital
yes
[Dark music fades]
[Jungheon] Professor!
[nervous music]
This patient too
I think you should take a look
I am the last survivor
Patients classified as
Everyone has started transporting
I'm bleeding too much
Is there any hope?
[sigh]
[Girl crying]
[Girl crying] Oppa
Please save my brother
Brother!
[Girl crying]
[Rescuer] Professor!
open fracture patient
I will leave for Korea University Hospital.
Are you going to go with me?
[Jungheon] Hey, Professor
From patients with greater likelihood
Shouldn't I have surgery?
This patient was transferred to another hospital...
no
If it's not me, I can't save this patient.
[Joongheon] Then that patient
What should I do?
Besides, earlier
Patients transferred to Korea University Hospital
Things weren't good, weren't they?
[Rough breathing]
[helicopter sound]
This patient is also going to Korea University Hospital.
all three patients
I have to survive
[The tense music fades]
[Yurim] Oh my, it smells good
- Umm, stop eating, I'm full.
- [Mobile phone vibrating sound]
Oh well, this is such a waste
- What if I don’t eat this?
- [Sound of clattering down]
I need to stick to my bones, just wait.
Oh my, who is this!
the savior of our lives
Isn’t this Professor Baek Kang-hyuk, huh?
[Kang Hyuk] Open fracture patient!
Is there anyone who can help me?
Anyone want to help me?
Well, can someone help me?
Who is there now?
Is it possible to recruit an orthopedic professor?
[Yurim] I guess he’s having surgery? The resident...
- No, not as a resident.
- [Yurim] If you don’t become a resident,
Who should I invite?
[Sound of bitter mouth]
- [Kang Hyuk] No, professor.
- Oh, well.
[Kanghyuk] Oh, really
It's because it's too serious
Let's do a favor.
[Yurim] Oh, okay
- I got it.
- [Kang Hyuk] Oh, and
The chief is also preparing for surgery.
Who?
me?
Well, please come into the operating room.
[Yurim] I’m an anal surgeon.
It’s been a while since I had a scalpel
[Kang Hyuk] Because it’s no joke
Get ready quickly
- [Call end sound]
- Ugh!
Uh, Professor Baek!
kid!
This is really, this…
He always quits first, this...
[Tsk mouth sound]
- [Jiyoung] Dad
- Huh?
[Jiyoung] Why?
No, that…
Oh, I don't have enough hands
They told me to come into the operating room.
[Jiyoung] Yes
I don't know if I can wear it
I completely agree
Why did I go to medical school?
my dad
The way he held the scalpel was so cool
Yeah?
[Yurim] Uh, uh, is it finished?
[Junsu] I won’t do it
[Yurim] Hey, don’t do that, okay?
[Junsu] I couldn’t even eat a single meal today
Surgery already today
Do you know how many cases were done?
- [rattling button sound]
- [Yurim] Oh my, that’s right.
- Hey, you know, don't do that, okay?
- [rattling button sound]
- [The sound of water stops]
- Boy, the patient has to be saved, right?
- [Sound of rubbing hands]
-Patient has an open fracture
You know that only Professor Jeong can save you, right?
- uh? help me
- [Knocking sound]
Help me, okay?
Come quickly, I'll be there first.
- [Sound of footsteps moving away]
- Huh?
Why did that guy change like this?
[telephone ringing sound]
[Interesting music]
Yes, anesthesiology
[Indifferently] Ah…
[Whispering] Hey, why, why?
[very small] emergency surgery
[Whispering] They say I’m not there
Yeah, I don't have it
[Very softly] I don't have it
[Doctor] Oh, what should I do?
We are fully booked
There are so many surgeries today.
-What room is it?
- [Music stops]
Ah, yes, that teacher Park Kyung-won
I asked how many times I had a room.
Ah, yes, I understand.
[Sound of putting down receiver]
emergency operating room
[Sunwoo] Hey, it’s crazy
Aren't you even annoyed?
Hey, I'm behind schedule.
Suddenly put in an emergency
Because it’s literally an emergency
I have no choice but to throw it in suddenly.
[Sunwoo] What, man?
Legally prepared for emergency surgery
How many people are in the anesthesiology department?
Aren't you supposed to wait?
And yet everything
It's by reservation only.
If it's wrong, it's wrong.
[Sunwoo] Oh, but this bastard, hey
Hey, don't you come here?
Hey, tight!
- [Business broadcast notification sound]
- [Sigh]
[Guidance voice plays]
Hello, manager
At this moment
If you're going this way
Trauma surgery?
yes
[Anesthesia Manager] Don’t go.
Why are you doing that?
[Head of Anesthesia] Trauma Center
Announcement of recruitment of full-time anesthesiologists
Did you know that there has been no support for two years?
[dark music]
those people
Don't torture hope
go back
I'll send another doctor to the operating room.
[Dark music fades]
[sigh]
[dark music]
[Nurse] Uh, Professor!
- [Kang Hyuk] What about anesthesiology?
- [Nurse] Oh, yes, not yet.
[Kang Hyuk] Oh my...
[Nurse] One, two, three
[Fast ECG beep sound]
- [Automatic door sound]
- [Yurim] Uh, Professor Baek
Uh, manager.
Please take care of my lower abdomen here.
[Yurim] Me, me, look at me
Do this surgery now?
Ai, that, in anal surgery
You do a lot of rectal surgeries.
[Yurim] Uh, fish oil
Is this a bit difficult?
Oh, it's okay, go down quickly.
[Yurim] Oh, okay, okay.
Mr. I
-Why isn’t the anesthesiology department coming? Mr.
- [Automatic door sound]
[Kyungwon] Anesthesia
Let's start with popolo.
- [Kang Hyuk] Oh, quickly, quickly.
- [Heavy music]
[Kyungwon] Popol is entering.
[Yurim] Just stay still
Me, what should I do first?
Now I'm checking the bleeding area, I'm stopping it
and the lower part of the palm
Are you blocking it?
[Yurim] Uh, now, now, like this?
[Kanghyuk] I wash my hands
Just hold on until it comes
- [Yurim] Okay
- [Kang Hyuk] 3 minutes at most
- 3 minutes
- [Yurim] Oh, oh, I understand
- [Yurim] Oh! uh!
[Embarrassed sounds] Quick, quick, uh!
Quick, quick!
Hey, hey
Ugh!
[automatic door sound]
[Kang Hyuk] Hold on just a little bit, just a little bit, please
[Yurim] Hey, hey! slipping
Hey, this
- [Kanghyuk] Please
- [Yurim’s embarrassed voice]
Mr…
- [Sound of blood gushing]
- [Yurim] Hey, quickly, quickly.
Hey, blood pressure is dropping, blood pressure!
[Yurim’s heavy breathing]
[Kang Hyuk] What are you doing!
I told you to hold on for 3 minutes
A person who has lived his entire life by eating swords and rice
Can't you do that?
[Yurim] Hurry up
Please do something, quickly
- [Kanghyuk] One, two
- [Yurim’s sound of strength]
Uh, okay, hold on tight
scalpel
[Nurse] Yes, it is here.
- [Kang Hyuk] I'm going to have a laparotomy.
- [Yurim gasps] Uh
- [Kang Hyuk] Hold on well.
- [Yurim] Okay
[Yurim’s repeated heavy breathing]
[Reporter] Meanwhile, the tour bus
falling down the leg
- [Music fades]
- Even though it was a major accident
The reason there were few deaths was
Medical staff are quickly dispatched to the scene
Golden time on site
It was because I protected it.
I understand
Minister of Health and Welfare Kang Myung-hee said:
transferred to each hospital
in the treatment of patients
I asked you to do your best.
yes, i am now
It's in front of Korea University Hospital.
Injuries are particularly severe here.
3 severe trauma patients
I'm in emergency surgery.
[Heavy music]
dispatched directly to the scene of the accident
According to the judgment of Professor Baek Kang-hyuk of Korea University,
These are patients who were urgently transferred.
All three patients were blind
Known for being quarrelsome
[Continuous rattling sound]
[Yurim] Shame
[Kang Hyuk] If you catch bleeding, here is the upper abdomen.
Let's start right away with the spleen
[Yurim] Yes, okay
[Kang Hyuk] Oh my, my hands
Why is it so slow? Quickly!
[Yurim] Hey, me too
I'm doing my best
[Kang Hyuk’s tsk mouth and sigh]
[Kanghyuk] I know it’s the best
But just a little more
[Yurim] Damn it
No, why are you in such a hurry?
[Kang Hyuk] I’m a little busy.
[Jaewon] I stopped the bleeding
I will remove the pipe
[Jaewon’s heavy breathing]
[Inhaler operating sound]
[Kang Hyuk] To No. 1
To join as soon as possible
I have to hurry, is there anything I can do?
Now, spleen suturing is complete.
- cut
- [Woman] Yes
[Yurim] What, are you done already?
[Kang Hyuk] First of all, I put out the urgent fire.
Let’s go into the lower abdomen together.
[Yurim] Ah, yes, I understand…
[Laughing] Oh, I
Respectfully... [Clears cough]
[Kang Hyuk] Has the bleeding not been completely controlled?
[Doctor] Yes, inside the retroperitoneum.
I keep bleeding.
[Kang Hyuk] Ai, you’re busy.
[Yurim] What is it?
What is this, this?
Can I continue?
Is this bleeding okay?
[Kang Hyuk] Boy, I looked at the bleeding area.
I feel like my adrenal glands are completely crushed.
[Beeping warning sound]
[Yurim] What is it?
[Kyungwon] Professor, my heart rate is rising.
- [Yurim] What should I do? Professor Baek
- [Continuous beeping warning sound]
[Gyeongwon] ABP 160
- [Kanghyuk] Damn you, Mr.
- [Gyeongwon] 180
[Yurim] What is this?
What happened to this?
On the adrenal side
What's the problem now?
[Kang Hyuk] I think this patient is a cancer patient.
Lymphatics is leaking
[Yurim] Huh? Limphatics!
Hey, hey, I'm in a mess, I'm in a mess
How can I do this quickly, now?
- [Kang Hyuk] Forceps, Metzen
- [Gyeongwon] ABP 190, 200
[Yurim] Oh! How much is your blood pressure?
Hey, hey, now
on the lower abdomen
Bleeding is no joke, now.
Awesome, man, this
Hey, now, why are you like this, right here…
[Gyeongwon] At SINUS
Go to Aridmia, ventricular tachycardia
[Yurim] How much is your blood pressure?
Is this okay as is, now?
- [Kang Hyuk] Tai
- [Woman] Yes
[Continuous beeping warning sound]
[Kyungwon] Beta blocker is being installed.
First, stop the bleeding as much as possible.
[Yurim] Professor Baek!
[Kanghyuk] Bobby
Forceps, quickly
[Yu-rim] Professor Baek, do something!
[Kang Hyuk] Wait a minute.
Now the adrenal glands themselves
Because I'm taking it off
[Yurim] Huh? Are you sane? uh?
It could go wrong, now
What are you thinking!
Professor Baek
Professor Baek! Think well, huh?
If you remove the adrenal glands by mistake...
Professor Baek!
hey! Baekgyo…
[Yurim’s surprised gasp]
Back…
[Constant ECG beeping sound]
Is it done?
[Kang Hyuk] What is your blood pressure?
[Gyeongwon] ABP 180
It falls little by little
[Yurim sighs in relief]
[Kang Hyuk] Beta Blocker
How much did it cost?
- [Music fades]
- [Kyungwon] 5 milligrams.
Is the sap loaded at full capacity?
Now 30 seconds have passed
10 more minutes to go
I'll keep it at about 500 millimeters.
[Kanghyuk] It’s just right
[Sound of wind blowing]
Now let's wrap it up
[Yurim clears her throat]
[Yurim] Okay, let’s suture it quickly.
[Kanghyuk] No
The manager told me to finish it alone.
Because I have to go to number 1.
[Yurim] What are you talking about?
Are you telling me to do this alone?
[Kang Hyuk] First of all, vital signs have stabilized.
For the rest, I get help from Teacher Park.
this patient
He saved half of my life.
[Sound of taking off gloves]
[Snap sound]
[Yurim] Are you really going?
[automatic door sound]
Uh, I'm Baek Kang-hyuk.
How is the surgery going now?
[Nurse] Uh, do your best.
I'm doing everything, but
[Jaewon] Oh! Oh, there's blood, blood!
gauze please
[Rose] I’ll also replace the blood pack!
- [Nurse’s urgent voice]
- [Jaewon] Please increase the suction power.
[Kang Hyuk] Hello
Hey, hey!
Mr. I
What should I do if I hang up like this, Mr.
[heavy music]
[Jaewon’s heavy breathing]
[Jaewon] It keeps coming, press it!
[Doctor] Yes, yes
[Jaewon] I found it, take it out, take it out, take it out, take it out!
- Okay, la…
- [Rose] Right angle.
[Jaewon] Yes
[Jaewon’s heavy breathing]
And that…
[Jaewon’s stuttering sound]
[Rose] Are you looking for suture number 3?
[Jaewon gasps] Thank you
[automatic door sound]
[Kang Hyuk] What’s wrong with blood?
- [Jaewon] Ah!
- [Heavy music stops]
Uh, professor
[Kanghyuk] Take that hand away
I can't see the screen
Look, that's still there
I'm wandering in the mesentery
[Jaewon] Oh, that’s…
This is cut in half
[Kang Hyuk] I’ll lose everything that was cut.
You can just go in.
[Sound of putting on gloves]
When I tie my tie like that, my blood starts to burst.
Fat and arteries
Must be completely separated
[Jaewon] Oh, I was in a hurry earlier…
[Kanghyuk] Go to your seat
[Jaewon] Yes?
[Kang Hyuk] Die Sector
No. 1
- [Jaewon] Yes
- [Kang Hyuk] Look carefully.
[clattering sound]
If blood vessels are visible through fatty tissue
In this way, at the wound site
It has to be tied within 1cm.
[Jaewon] Yes
[Jaewon sighs]
[Junsu] Suction
- [Inhaler operating sound]
- [Slow ECG beep sound]
[Anesthetist] Professor
Ikeiji is sagging.
[heavy music]
[Junsu] Why is Ikeiji sagging?
What, why are you like this?
Hey, prepare epi and atropine.
Take out the defibrillator
- Launch Code Blue, quickly!
- [Woman] Yes, I understand!
[Guide voice] Code blue, code blue
Main building operating room room 25
[Kang Hyuk] No. 1, the place you touched earlier.
Tie it all up again
Take a good look inside, okay?
If you think it's okay
remaining bleeding area
Hold and close, okay?
[Jaewon] Yes?
Professor, where are you going?
[Sound of repeatedly taking off gloves]
Where are you going!
[Junsu] No, right leg
No problem
I stopped the bleeding a long time ago.
What's the problem?
uh?
[Guide voice] Code blue, code blue
Main building operating room room 25
Code blue, code blue
[Anesthetist] Rhythm is back
- [Junsu] Huh? [Sigh of relief]
- [Music fades]
Hey, hey, they said they were back, they said they were back
Come down, come down, come down
Who is it?
Professor Baek Kang-hyuk?
[Kang Hyuk] Yes
What is the patient's condition?
[Anesthetist] Respiratory rate is determined by device settings.
I'm maintaining it at 11 times per minute.
Gas exchange not possible
Saturation drops to 60
[Kanghyuk’s deep breathing]
[Kang Hyuk] Besides diabetes
You said you don’t have any other underlying diseases, right?
- [Anesthetist] Yes.
- [Kanghyuk] Give him full oxygen
Start heparin loading
[Anesthetist] Heparin?
[Kanghyuk] Don’t ask again, quickly
[Anesthetist] Okay.
[Junsu] Me, Professor Baek
Well, please explain the current situation...
- [Monoton music]
- [Kang Hyuk sighs] Fractures and
This type of blood vessel damage
If they occur at the same time
What are the possibilities?
There's oil inside the bones.
But when the bone broke
It's going to flow into your veins.
[Junsu] That’s right!
Then it passes through the right atrium and right ventricle.
By blocking the pulmonary artery
Pulmonary embolism occurs.
[Kang Hyuk] You know very well, as expected.
[Junsu] That’s right
[Woman] Heparin injection completed
[Anesthetist] Saturation goes up
[Kang Hyuk] I’ve passed the hurdle
I'll take the left leg.
- Please do the drape again.
- [Man] Yes
[Junsu] This is an open fracture
No one can do surgery
[Kang Hyuk] So,
So I will do it
[The monotonous music fades]
[Jaewon sighs]
- [Rose] Teacher Jaewon
- [Jaewon] Hmm?
[Rose] Don’t be too upset
That guy is really picky.
[Jaewon] Still
This was my first patient.
[The rose is eating away]
[Rose] If you do well from the beginning
Why are you a fellow? professor not
[Jaewon] Is that so?
[Rose Sigh]
Don't you remember earlier, how much blood loss?
[The Lament of the Rose]
That's just 4 packs of blood
Because it was blocked.
I'm honest
Until the professor comes
Is the patient alive?
I was skeptical.
But you're alive
Well done
[Jaewon’s shy breathing]
[Sound of Jaewon taking a deep breath]
[Jaewon] Thank you, teacher
Even though it was a large-scale disaster, the number of deaths was
The reason there were relatively few
dispatched directly to the scene
Professor Baek Kang-hyuk’s…
Currently transferred to Korea University Hospital
3 seriously ill patients
I'm in emergency surgery
I'm watching the situation
I told you
Minister of Health and Welfare Kang Myung-hee...
[Noisy sound]
[Jaehoon] Oh, really, Mr...
Ah, I need to fix this.
What are you going to do about this?
- I'm going crazy, really.
- Uh, Manager Lim!
uh! Mr. Keynote Manager
Hey, outside the emergency center...
[Jaehoon] Sowol Bridge!
What is the situation in the operating room for those seriously injured?
That's exactly what I am...
[Jaehoon] No, this guy
Emergency medicine department chief
If you don't know the emergency room patients, who knows?
[Manager Lim] Oh, that’s not it, that…
The seriously injured person was in charge of Professor Baek...
On our side
We only support auxiliary staff.
Oh, more than that
Outside the emergency center...
Ah, that's it!
What happens so quickly?
Take a look
No, Professor Baek
What if there's an accident, huh?
The image of this hospital, huh?
uh?
[Majestic music]
Oh, what!
Boy, has anyone been seriously injured?
It's only 3 hours now
Are you already out of the operating room?
[Surprised gasp]
- Table death?
- [The majestic music stops]
[Jaehoon] Week, week, week...
- Joo, are you dying?
- [Heavy sound effect]
Three, all three?
- Oh my.
- [Uneasy sound effect]
- Oh my, director.
- Director Keynote, are you okay?
- I…
- [Jaehoon’s heavy breathing]
[Jaewon] Uh, uh
Hello, hello
Baekgang…
Baek, Baek Kang, Baek Kang Hyuk!
What is that, that bastard, that!
[Manager Lim] Hey, Chief of Staff
That, no
- [Jaehoon] Stand there, hey, Baekgang…
- [Manager Lim] Outside, there…
- Chief of Keynote!
- [Jaehoon] Baek Kanghyuk!
Baekgang…
- Baekgang…
- [Camera shutter sound clicking]
[Noisy sound]
[Reporters’ questions]
The man behind it! Get out of the way, get out of the way
- Man... [Grunting sound]
- [Manager Lim] Chief of Staff
- [Continuously noisy]
- [Jaehoon] Ahyu
What are these?
Reporters wait for Professor Baek’s surgery to be over.
They were waiting
[Jaehoon] Why?
- [Manager Lim] Sowol Bridge seriously injured…
- [Sound of surprise]
No way in front of this many people
Death announcement?
Oh, no way, no way…
That idiot, that one
[Suho] How is the patient’s condition?
[Reporter 1] About the progress of the surgery
Please say something
[Kang Hyuk] Okay, everyone.
Please pay attention
To the trauma center today
Three patients transferred
all
- lived
- [Reporters' exclamation]
[Reporter 2] Please look here.
- [Reporter 3] Of course, of course, Baek Kang-hyuk
- [Reporter 4] What’s going on?
[Reporters continue to admire]
not me
we did it together
Yes?
This is teacher Jaewon Yang.
A patient with a pipe stuck in his abdomen
He helped me with the surgery.
[Reporters' exclamation]
[Reporter 5] Teacher Jaewon Yang
Just this one time
- Please take a look
- [Kanghyuk] Straighten your back
- Yes, Professor.
- [Reporter 6] Please say something.
- [Reporter 7] Please smile once.
- [Calm music]
[Reporter 8] Here, once here too
Please take a look
[News Anchor] Korea University Hospital
Professor Baek Kang-hyuk's
Sowol Bridge Seriously Injured Person Surgery
all successfully
The news is that it is finished.
As a result, Professor Baek Kang-hyuk
- To the people again
- [Female student] Isn’t this really awesome?
[News anchor] Deep impression
I left it behind
Should I go to medical school too?
Besides me and Teacher Jaewon Yang here,
Including nurses
Thank you for your hard work in unseen places
There are medical staff
Especially from this person
I learned dedication
trauma center
Nurse Cheon Mi-mi
[Sparkling sound effect]
Also chronic
Due to lack of manpower at the trauma center
Difficult to deal with today
Thank you for your willingness to help in any situation
Chief of Surgery
With Professor Yurim Han
To Dr. Kyeong-won Park of the Department of Anesthesiology and Pain Medicine
Deep…
We would like to express our deepest gratitude.
A trauma center is a team
If I were alone like today
Things that would have been impossible
Because we have each other
It was possible
Please
I would like to ask you to
same as now
Your warm interest
more people
Make it salvageable
It's you
It is also about saving
At Korea University Hospital
Not satisfied with this achievement
Try harder
To meet the expectations of our citizens
To become a major trauma center
As the first step in starting
- [Soothing music fades]
- Full-time trauma surgeon and
Securing always-available medical staff
I promise you first
[Humorous sound effects]
[Kanghyuk ventriloquizes] Smile
It's me
[Muttering] They're leaving out the last bucks, really.
[Small] Professor
That means, that...
[With ventriloquism] Trauma surgery
Let's make our dream come true
- Huh? Chief of Keynote!
- [Interesting Music]
[Reporters muttering]
- Please take a look here.
[Kang Hyuk] Uh, our hospital’s trauma center is
Even with a short budget
I'm doing my best
So that we can go back better
[Emphasis clearly] Recruitment of manpower
I would like to suggest this.
[Mumbling] Oh, yeah
Ah, no, no, no, no
- No, that's... [Embarrassed sound]
- [Reporter 1] Please say one word!
- [Requests from reporters pour in]
- [Jaehoon] Ah, that…
[Laughing awkwardly] Oh, yeah
That, that… [Sound of bitter mouth]
[Reporter 2] Chief of Staff
Take a look here!
[Jaehoon stumbles] That’s it
It's beyond my authority, yeah...
- Discuss with the director...
- [A barrage of questions]
[Kang Hyuk] That’s right
Director Choi Jo-eun
Are you watching it now?
Please
[Kanghyuk ventriloquizes in the video] Smile
[Jo Eun] Baek Kang-hyuk…
Are you going to come out like this?
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Interesting music heightens]
[Reporter 1] Please take a look here!
[Reporter 2] Oh, please look this way!
[Continuously noisy]
[Reporter 3] Teacher, look here!
[Interesting music fades out]
[upbeat music]